[{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678862956,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":8130,"timeElapsed":46852},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678865430,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":2472,"timeElapsed":49326},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678869719,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":4287,"timeElapsed":53615},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678875974,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":6253,"timeElapsed":59870},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678880551,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":4574,"timeElapsed":64447},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678886807,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":6253,"timeElapsed":70702},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678894591,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":7782,"timeElapsed":78487},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678900994,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":6400,"timeElapsed":84889},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678906605,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":5609,"timeElapsed":90500},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678917316,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":9313,"timeElapsed":101211},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678919667,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":2349,"timeElapsed":103563},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678922506,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2837,"timeElapsed":106402},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678929210,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":6701,"timeElapsed":113105},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678949731,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":20519,"timeElapsed":133627},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678957650,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":7917,"timeElapsed":141546},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678966872,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":9220,"timeElapsed":150768},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678971390,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4516,"timeElapsed":155286},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678977568,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":6176,"timeElapsed":161464},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678984485,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":6915,"timeElapsed":168380},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679022899,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":37408,"timeElapsed":206795},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679027310,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":4409,"timeElapsed":211206},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679033142,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":5831,"timeElapsed":217038},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679038918,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":5774,"timeElapsed":222814},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679045849,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":6929,"timeElapsed":229745},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679063965,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":18114,"timeElapsed":247861},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679069337,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":5370,"timeElapsed":253233},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679076659,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":7320,"timeElapsed":260555},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679081907,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":5247,"timeElapsed":265803},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679091072,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":7813,"timeElapsed":274968},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679094552,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3477,"timeElapsed":278448},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679098318,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":3764,"timeElapsed":282214},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679106462,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":8142,"timeElapsed":290358},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679110166,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":3702,"timeElapsed":294062},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679116271,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":6103,"timeElapsed":300167},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679120788,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":4515,"timeElapsed":304684},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679129741,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":8951,"timeElapsed":313637},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679136866,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":7123,"timeElapsed":320762},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679143946,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":5893,"timeElapsed":327842},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679146661,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2713,"timeElapsed":330557},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679149768,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":3104,"timeElapsed":333664},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679152676,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":2906,"timeElapsed":336572},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679155120,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":2443,"timeElapsed":339016},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679158093,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":2970,"timeElapsed":341988},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679167436,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":9341,"timeElapsed":351332},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679170465,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":3027,"timeElapsed":354361},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679173406,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2938,"timeElapsed":357301},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679182827,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":7874,"timeElapsed":366723},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679194828,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":11999,"timeElapsed":378724},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679199445,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":4615,"timeElapsed":383341},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679205507,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":6059,"timeElapsed":389403},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679214295,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":8787,"timeElapsed":398191},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679219398,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":5100,"timeElapsed":403294},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679232567,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":13168,"timeElapsed":416463},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679236557,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":3988,"timeElapsed":420453},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679241760,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":5200,"timeElapsed":425656},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679255844,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":12970,"timeElapsed":439740},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679259415,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":3568,"timeElapsed":443311},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679268987,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":9571,"timeElapsed":452883},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679273037,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":4048,"timeElapsed":456933},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679275570,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2530,"timeElapsed":459465},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679278511,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":2940,"timeElapsed":462407},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679282576,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":4064,"timeElapsed":466472},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679286628,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":4050,"timeElapsed":470524},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679291830,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":5200,"timeElapsed":475726},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679303200,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":8247,"timeElapsed":487096},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679305164,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":1962,"timeElapsed":489060},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679313131,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":7964,"timeElapsed":497027},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679319975,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":6841,"timeElapsed":503871},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679325585,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":5608,"timeElapsed":509481},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679334421,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":8834,"timeElapsed":518317},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679351732,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":17309,"timeElapsed":535628},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679355694,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":3959,"timeElapsed":539589},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679360462,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4767,"timeElapsed":544358},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679366133,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":5669,"timeElapsed":550029},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679396984,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":29531,"timeElapsed":580880},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679399281,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":2296,"timeElapsed":583176},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679401681,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2399,"timeElapsed":585577},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679405746,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":4063,"timeElapsed":589641},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679408791,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":3044,"timeElapsed":592687},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679411971,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":3178,"timeElapsed":595867},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679415601,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":3628,"timeElapsed":599497},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679420099,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":4497,"timeElapsed":603995},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679423819,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":3717,"timeElapsed":607715},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679431067,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":5459,"timeElapsed":614963},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679434169,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":3100,"timeElapsed":618065},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679437169,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2998,"timeElapsed":621065},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679441190,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":4018,"timeElapsed":625086},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679447311,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":6119,"timeElapsed":631207},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679450566,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3253,"timeElapsed":634462},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679456852,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":6284,"timeElapsed":640748},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679468894,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":12040,"timeElapsed":652790},{"subjectID":"mcbvboc7z6","prolificID":"675cf786b9fb0e4f223877c1","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4db5b14e7a0561f7d7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679475106,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":6210,"timeElapsed":659002}]